Guide to the Kenneth J. Arrow Papers, 1939-2011
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Kenneth J. Arrow papers 1939-2011
Arrow, Kenneth J., 1921-
72.8 linear feet Extent: circa 43,250 Items
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
RL.00052
Language: English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The Correspondence, Consulting, and Personal Files Series are RESTRICTED.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The papers of Kenneth J. Arrow were donated to the Duke University David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library beginning in 1994.
Biographical Note
1921 Born in New York, NY
1940 B.S., Mathematics, City College of New York
1941 M.A., Mathematics, Columbia University
1942-1946 Weather Officer, US Army Air Corps (ret. Captain)
1947 Married Selma Schweitzer
1947-1949 Research Associate, Cowles Commission for Research in Economics
1948-1949 Assistant Professor of Economics, University of Chicago
1948- Consultant, the RAND Corporation
1949-1968 Acting Assistant Professor, Associate Professor, and Professor of Economics and Statistics, Stanford University
1951 Ph.D., Economics, Columbia University
1951 Publication: Social Choice and Individual Values
1954 Publication (with G. Debreu): Existence of Equilibrium for a Competitive Economy, Econometrica, vol. 22, pp. 265-290.
1957 Awarded John Bates Clark Medal by the American Economics Association (AEA)
1962-1963 Economist, President's Council of Economic Advisers
1968-1979 Professor of Economics, Harvard University
1972 Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences
1973 President, American Economics Association (AEA)
1980 to date Professor of Economics and Operations Research, Stanford University
1983-1986 President, International Economic Association (IEA)
Arrow has also been a fellow of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences and a member of the National Academy of Sciences.
Collection Overview
The Kenneth J. Arrow papers, 1939-2011 (bulk 1980s-1995), document primarily the latter part of his career as an economist, professor, and Nobel Laureate. The collection provides a broad overview of his many professional activities; administrative activities for various associations and committees and for his universities; and political activism in research notes, draft papers and speeches, and correspondence. Arrow's career is especially distinguished by his contributions to the theory of social choice, including his book Social Choice and Individual Values, published in 1951, and his contributions to general equilibrium theory. For these achievements, Professor Arrow has been awarded the Johns Bates Clark Medal (1957) and the Nobel Memorial Prize in Economics (1972), which he shared with Professor Sir John Hicks. With an eleven year interruption at Harvard University from 1968 to 1979, Professor Arrow has spent the largest portion of his career at Stanford University. He has served as president of the American Economics Association and the International Economics Association, and has also been a member of the National Academy of Sciences. Some of the larger and more salient files in the collection include research notes on general equilibrium theory in economics; consulting on global climate change and contingent valuation; correspondence with Frank Hahn, Leonid Hurwicz, Alain Lewis, and Lionel McKenzie; and notes from graduate courses with Harold Hotelling. Although the collection contains primarily professional papers, there are some personal files as well as some concerning politics and activism.
The Conferences, Lectures, and Speeches Series includes information on organizations such as the Santa Fe Institute, National Bureau of Economic Research, Social Choice and Welfare Conference, American Economics Association, and International Economics Association. General equilibrium theory material is in scattered files not only in this series but also in the Notes, Papers, and Research Series.
In the Committees and Consulting Series contain files on three extended projects on economic growth and policy, global climate change, and contingent valuation. Also, the American Economics Association, International Economics Association, and the National Academy of Sciences are represented. There is a subseries on economics journals.
The Correspondence and Personal Files Series includes correspondence with a number of eminent economists, including M. Allais, G. Debreu, M. Friedman, F. Hahn, J. Harsanyi, L. Hurwicz, T. Koopmans, L. McKenzie, R. Marschak, and R. Radner; with other scholars such as N. Chomskey, S.J. Gould, and J. Hirschleifer; with politicians, including D.P. Moynihan; as well as extensive notes and correspondence with some of Arrow's Ph.D. students, including A. Lewis.
In the Notes, Papers, and Research Series are notes on production functions, stability, uncertainty; economic theory, optimization, and decentralization; National Science Foundation grants; Social Choice and Multicriterion Decision-Making; and notes from courses with Harold Hotelling.
Departments of Economics are represented in the Stanford and Harvard Series, and the Miscellaneous Series has a folder on Arrow's Nobel Prize and other awards. The Politics and Activism Series contains files on the Middle East, arms control (especially Economists against the Arms Race), human rights, and UNESCO.
Additions to the collection have been intellectually integrated into their corresponding series but are physically housed separately in boxes 38-53.
Subject Headings
Harvard University. Dept. of Economics; Stanford University. Dept. of Economics; International Economics Association; Social choice; Economics -- Sociological aspects; Economics; Contingent valuation; Economists -- United States; Social action; Equilibrium (Economics); Climatic changes; Hahn, Frank; Hurwicz, Leonid; Hotelling, Harold, 1895-; Lewis, Alain A.; McKenzie, Lionel W.
Contents of Collection
- Conferences, Lectures, and Speeches Series, 1971-1995 (bulk 1980s-1995).
  Documents many of Professor Arrow's public speaking engagements and activities at conferences, especially after 1980. These include regular conferences organized by the American Economics Association, the Econometrics Society, the International Economics Association, the National Bureau of Economic Research, the Sante Fe Institute, and other institutions, as well as other trips and engagements.
  - Invitations Declined (Box 1)
  - Invitations Declined, 1993-2005, (9 folders) (Box 38)
  - Abrahms Lectures (Box 1)
  - Abrahms Lectures, 1984-1991 (Box 38)
  - Actuaries Club (Box 1)
  - American Economics Association (AEA) Meeting, Dallas, 1984 (Box 1)
  - AEA
    - Economics Theory Session, 1989 (Box 1)
    - 1990 (Box 1)
    - Meeting, Anaheim, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Meeting, Boston, 1994 (Ely Lecture) (Box 1)
    - Meeting, Washington, DC, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Affaires Mondales, 1994 (Box 38)
  - AIDS Conference-Kirman, 2003 (Box 38)
  - All Souls College, 1996 (Box 38)
  - Amsterdam Royal, 1997 (Box 38)
  - APSA meeting, 1997 (Box 38)
  - Arrow- Hurwicz Workshop, 1977 (Informational Issues in Decentralization) (Box 1)
  - Associated Students of Stanford University (ASSU) Conference, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Australia, 1998 (Box 38)
  - Barcelona Lecture, 1990 (Excellence and Equity in Education) (Box 1)
  - Barcelona, 1999 (Box 38)
  - Basel Conference, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Behavioral Foundations of Economic Theory, 1984-85 (Rationality of Self and Others) (Box 1)
  - Beijer-Asko, 2007 (Box 38)
  - Beijer-Asko, 2008 (Box 38)
  - Beijer-Sandee, 2003 (Box 38)
  - Beijer-Venice, 1997 (Box 38)
  - Beijer-Yucatan, 2001 (Box 38)
  - Bellagio Conference, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Bergen, 2001 (Box 38)
  - Berlin WBZ Lecture, 1994 (Box 38)
  - Bruno memorial, 1997 (Box 38)
  - Camp Lecture, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Camp Lectures, 1980 (Possibility of Economic Policy) (Box 1)
  - Carey Lecture, 1996 (Box 38)
  - Catastrophic Risk, 1994 (Box 38)
  - Centennial Symposia, 1990 (Information Explosion) (Box 1)
  - Center for Economic Policy Research, 1986-87 (Economics of Public Debt) (Box 1)
  - CERES Conference on Global Food and Technology Issues in the 21st Century, Williamsburg, 1990 (Box 1)
  - CERGE-EI, 1996 (Box 38)
  - Chinese Information Science, 1992 (Box 2)
  - China Trip Diary, 1979 (Box 2)
  - China Conference, 2000 (Box 38)
  - Collegium Budapest, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Complexity Workshop, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Conflict Resolution Conference, 2001 (Box 38)
  - Contingent Valuation Method Conference, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Cornell Talk, 2001 (Box 38)
  - Corporation Conference, 1987 (Box 2)
  - Cowles Symposium, 1981-86 (Cowles in the History of Economic Thought) (Box 2)
  - Cyprus Visit, 2000 (Box 38)
  - Decision and Discretion Talk, 2001 (Box 38)
  - Differential Information, Market Failure, and Public Policy, 1977 (Box 2)
  - Disorder and Order, 1981 (Box 2)
  - Eastern Europe Conference, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Ecology and Economics, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Econometrics Society Meeting, Barcelona, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Econometrics Society Meeting, Korea, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Economic Conflict Program, Office of Naval Research, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Economics of Income Distribution, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Economics of National Security, 1986-88 (Box 2)
  - Edge Lecture (Box 2)
  - Elster Colloquium, 1985-86 (Box 2)
  - Elster Central Bank Conference, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Empirica, 1994 (Box 38)
  - Environmental Policy Decisions, 1990 (Environmental Policy As Political Conflict) (Box 2)
  - FACS Institute for Journalists, Asilomar, CA, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Federazione delle Associazioni Scientifiche e Tecniche (FAST) Meeting, Milan, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Florence, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Florence Bioethical Conference, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Ford Foundation, Future and the Welfare State, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Friedman Panel, 1987 (Box 2)
  - Fuchs Symposium, 1995 (Box 38)
  - Fulbright Siena, 1995 (Box 38)
  - Gamble Lecture, 1998 (Box 38)
  - Game Theory Congress, Bilbao, 2000 (Box 38)
  - General Equilibrium Conference, 1993 (Box 2)
  - German Business Congress, 1993-95 (Box 2)
  - German Trip, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Greater Talent Network, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Grunberg Lecture, 1994 (Economic Transition Speed and Scope) (Box 2)
  - Haavelmo Seminar, 2005 (Box 38)
  - Hamburg Seminar, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Hao Ran Foundation Workshop, 1989-90 (On the Socialist Economic Reform) (Incentive Problems in the Transition in Socialist Countries) (Box 2)
  - Harsanyi Conference, Berkeley, 1990-91 (Ethics in Business Contribution of John Harsanyi) (Box 2)
  - Health Economic Research Organization (HERO) Session, 1973 (Box 2)
  - Hicks Conference, 1988-90 (Certainty Equivalence and Inequivalence for Prices) (Box 2)
  - Hong Kong Lecture, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Hong Kong, 1996 (Box 38)
  - Hoover Anti-Trust Conference, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Hoover Conference on Economic Transition, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Hungarian Trip, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Hurwicz Fest, 2007 (Box 38)
  - Hypothesis, 1997 (Box 38)
  - Hypothesis, Milan, 2000 (Box 39)
  - International Economics Association (IEA) (Box 2)
    - Conference, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Conference on Incomes Policy, Mexico, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Congress Addresses, (2 folders) (Box 2,3)
    - Congress VIII, India, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 3,4)
    - Forthcoming Conferences (Box 4)
    - Social Choice Session, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Congress IX, Greece, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Partnership Conference, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Meade Conference, 1991 (Box 4)
    - Congress X, Information Economics, Moscow, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Congress X, Graduate Education, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Income Inequality Conference, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Rationality Conference, Turin, 1993 (Box 38)
  - India Trip, 1986-87 (Box 5)
  - Industrial Ecology, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Innovation Diffusion, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Institutions and Development, 2005 (Box 39)
  - Iowa Lecture, 1992 (Box 5)
  - International Environmental Policy Conference, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Interpersonal Comparability Conference, 1986-88 (Box 5)
  - International Society for Inventory Research, Economics of Inventory Management, Budapest, 1988 (Box 5)
  - IPMU, 1999 (Box 39)
  - Itineraries, 1991-04 (Box 39)
  - Jacques Lesourne Conference, 2000 (Box 39)
  - Japan Development Bank Symposium, 2005 (Box 39)
  - Jerusalem Summer Workshop, 1991 (Increasing Returns) (Box 39)
  - Jerusalem Summer Workshop, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Jerusalem Summer Workshop, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Jerusalem Summer Workshop, 1994-2001, (8 folders) (Box 39)
  - Jerusalem Summer Workshop, 2003-2010, (8 folders) (Box 39)
  - The Johnson Cluster Group, 2000 (Box 39)
  - Karlin Conference, 2004 (Box 39)
  - Karlsruhe Seminar, 1988-90 (Box 5)
  - Keynesian Workshop, 1978 (The State of Keynesian Economics) (Box 5)
  - Keystone Center, 1990-91 (Box 5)
  - Knoer Seminar, 1978 (Economies of Distributions) (Box 5)
  - Kochar Education Conference, 2001 (Box 39)
  - Koopman's Lecture, Austria, 1993 (Box 39)
  - Korea Development Institute, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Kyung Hee University, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Laffont Conference, 2005 (Box 39)
  - Lazarfeld Lecture, Columbia University, 1993 (Methodological Individualism An Adequate Basis for the Social Sciences?) (Box 5)
  - Leverhulme Symposium, 2009 (Box 39)
  - Limits of Economic Rationality, 1989 (Box 39)
  - Long Term Productivity Trends, 1989 (Box 5)
  - MacArthur, London, 2001 (Box 39)
  - Management Development Program, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Manne General Equilibrium Workshop, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Markets for Information, Ownership, and Control, 1988-89 (Box 5)
  - Maxwell Lecture, McGill University, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Meritocracy Conference, 1998 (Box 39)
  - Mexico Lecture, 1990 (Transitions from Socialism) (Box 5)
  - Michigan/Sante Fe Instititute (SFI) Outpost, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Milan, May 1995 (Box 39)
  - Miscellaneous Seminars, 1981-83 (Box 5)
  - MIT Honor, 2000 (Box 39)
  - MIT Visiting Professor, 1966 (Box 39)
  - Mitchell Madison, 1996 (Box 39)
  - Monash Increasing Returns Conference, 1996 (Box 39)
  - Monash University Visit, 1995 (Box 39)
  - Moscow Trip, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Mathematical Sciences Research Institute, 1985-86 (Box 5)
  - Naples Institute, 1999 (Box 39)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), Academy Forum, 1973-79 (Box 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), Industrial Ecology Conference, 1991 (Box 5)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER)
    - Conference, 1971-72 (Box 5)
    - Economic Fluctuations Meeting, 1987-88 (Box 5)
    - Conference on Econometrics and Mathematical Economics, 1990-91 (Box 6)
    - Economic Growth Conference, 1991 (Box 6)
    - General Equilibrium Conference, 1992 (Box 6)
    - 50th Anniversay Conference - Inventive, 2010 (Box 39)
  - Nemetria, Etica Ed Economia, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Neuberger Conference on the Structure and Behavior of Economic Organizations, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Nevada Kenney Talk, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Nobel Democracy Symposium, 1994 (Box 39)
  - Nonlinear Analysis Congress, 1991 (Box 6)
  - North Carolina Visit, 1986 (Box 39)
  - North Carolina Trip, 1988 (Box 6)
  - Notre Dame Income Distribution Conference, 1992 (The Changing Distribution of Income in an Open US Economy) (Box 6)
  - Office of Naval Research Symposium, 1986 (Box 6)
  - OHE Lecture, 2005 (Box 39)
  - Olin Lecture, 1988 (The Economics of Law) (Box 6)
  - Operations Research Symposium, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD) Conference, 1989 (Box 6)
  - ORSA/TIMS, Epistemic Uncertainty in Rational Decision, San Francisco, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Paris Trip, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Pioneers in Science, 2010 (Box 39)
  - Pisa (St. Anna), 2001 (Box 39)
  - Pittsburgh Lecture, Philosophy of Science, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Politico-Military Decision Making Workshop, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Pomona Lecture, 1988 (Economics and Ethics of Income Distribution) (Box 6)
  - Poverty Seminar (Box 6)
  - Public Choice Society (Box 39)
  - Queens University Talk, 1974-78 (Box 6)
  - RFF-EMF Discount Conference, 1996 (Box 39)
  - Royal Lectures, 1995 (Box 39)
  - Royal Economic Society Conference, London, 1991 (Box 6)
  - St. Norbert Conference, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Sabre Foundation, 1989 (Box 6)
  - San Diego State Talk, 1990 (Box 6)
  - San Francisco Mathematics Collaborative, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Santa Clara Lecture, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Santa Fe Institute
    - Evolutionary Paths of the Global Economy, 1987 (Box 6)
    - The Economy as an Evolving, Complex System, 1988 (Box 6)
    - The Economy as an Evolving, Complex System, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Global Security Workshop, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Growth and Cities Workshop, 1991 (Box 6)
    - Workshop on Learning, 1991 (Box 6)
    - Biology and Economics; Theoretical Computation in Economics, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Complex Adaptive Systems Workshop, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Increasing Returns Workshop, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Organizational Adaption and Learning Workshop, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Scarf 65th Birthday, 1995 (Box 39)
  - SCID-India, 2010 (Box 39)
  - Scitovsky Memorial, 2004 (Box 39)
  - Schneider Fest, 2005 (Box 39)
  - Seltzer Lecture, 1995 (Box 39)
  - SFI Evolving III, 2001 (Box 39)
  - Shanghai Academy of Social Science, 1998 (Box 39)
  - Shell Lecture, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Sheshinski Fest, 2006 (Box 39)
  - SIEPR Social Interaction Conference, 2008 (Box 39)
  - Sienna Conference, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Simon Entrepreneur Seminar, 1998 (Box 39)
  - Small and Large Firms in Innovation, 1997 (Box 39)
  - Social Choice and Welfare Conference, Caen, 1991 (Political Conditions for Economic Reform in Eastern Europe) (Box 6)
  - Social Choice Talk, ND (Box 39)
  - Socialist Agriculture, Budapest, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Society for Risk Analysis, 2009 (Box 39)
  - Southern Economic Association, 1981, (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Spoleto, Padua, 1987 (Information as a Service Industry) (Box 6)
  - Stanford Center on Conflict and Negotiation (SCCN), Conference on the Barriers to the Negotiated Resolution of Conflict, 1992-94 (Box 6)
  - Stanford Center on Conflict and Negotiation (SCCN), Conference on the Barriers to the Negotiated Resolution of Conflict, 1992-94, (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Stanford Institute of Theoretical Economics (SITE):
    - Workshop on Irreversibility, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Workshop, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Workshop on Economics of Inequality, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Workshop, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Strategic Economic Decisions Conference, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Stonybrook Game Theory Seminar, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Suzumura Fest, 2004 (Box 39)
  - Taiwan/ Hong Kong Trip, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Tanner Lecture:
    - Oxford, 1983 (The Welfare-Relevant Boundaries of the Individual) (Box 7)
    - Harvard, 1985 (The Unknown Other) (Box 7)
    - Harvard (audio tapes), 1985 (Box 7)
    - Stanford, 1986 (Box 7)
    - Grace, 1996 (Box 39)
  - Taplin Lecture, 2002 (Box 39)
  - Technion Guardians, 1992 (Israel's Economy in the Last Decade) (Box 7)
  - Tel Aviv University, 2001 (Box 39)
  - The Institute of Management Sciences (TIMS) Meeting, Rio de Janeiro, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Theories of Economic Justice Seminar (Box 7)
  - Toulouse, 1995 (Box 39)
  - Townsend Harris High School, 2004 (Box 39)
  - Transfer Programs, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Trinity University Lecture, 1984 (My Development as an Economist) (Box 7)
  - Tulane Lecture, 1980 (Box 39)
  - University of Calgary Speech, 1978 (Rational Discourse and Conflict in Values and Judgment) (Box 7)
  - University of California, Davis Lecture, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Weizmann Institute Dinner, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Western Economic Association Meetings, San Francisco, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Western Economic Association Meetings, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Western Michigan Talk, 1988-89 (The State of Economic Science) (Box 7)
  - Williams College Lecture, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Williamson Organization Conference, 1991 (Scale Returns in Communication and Elite Control of Organizations) (Box 7)
  - Williamson Conference, 1996 (Box 39)
  - Wingspread Conference, 1982 (Planning and Uncertainty) (Box 7)
  - Wisdom Toward the 21st Century Symposium, Osaka, 1983 (The International Economic Order of the 21st Century) (Box 7)
  - World Health Organization, Meeting on the Economics of Tropical Diseases, 1986 (Box 7)
- Committees and Consulting Series, 1980s-1990s.
  Includes both administrative work for various committees and institutions, as well as work as a paid consultant on several projects. The latter includes three extended projects, one on economic growth and policy for the Canadian Institute for Advanced Research, one on climate change for the National Academy of Sciences and one on contingent valuation (the use of surveys to value public goods) for the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Association. The former includes work for the American Economics Association and International Economics Association, as well as for the City College of New York, the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, RAND, the Santa Fe Institute, and other organizations. It also includes a Journals Subseries with Arrow's work on various editorial boards.
  - Abt Associates (Box 7)
  - Abt Associates, 1984-1986 (Box 40)
  - Abt Jobs (Box 7)
  - Aix-Marseille Center/GREQE (Box 7)
  - Alchian Tribute, 2001 (Box 40)
  - Alaska-National Energy Policy (Box 7)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 7)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences Western Center (Box 7)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences Western Center (Box 8)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences Nominations (Box 40)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (Box 8)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science-Electorate Nominating Committee, 1994-96 (Box 40)
  - American Association of University Professors (Box 8)
  - American Economics Association (AEA)
    - Committee on USSR Relations (Box 8)
    - Committee on Political Discrimination (Box 8)
    - Committee on Graduate Training (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 2004 (Box 40)
  - AEA/Social Sciences Research Council (Box 8)
    - China Exchange (Box 8)
    - Chinese-American Exchange, 1991 (Box 40)
    - South African Students (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
  - American Federation of Sciences, 1997 (Box 40)
  - American Foreign Policy Inc. (Box 8)
  - American Philosophical Society (Box 8)
  - American Society for Technion Israel Institute of Technology (Box 8)
  - American Statistical Association (Box 8)
  - Arrow Prize (Berkeley), 2004-05 (Box 40)
  - Banca Nazionale Del Lavoro Quarterly Review, 1993 (Box 40)
  - Beijer- Excess Consumption, 2004, (3 folders) (Box 40)
  - Beijer Institute, 1993-2002 (Box 40)
  - Ben-Gurion University of the Negev, Board of Governors, 1993-1998 (Box 40)
  - Berkeley Mathematical Sciences Research Institute (Box 8)
  - Bioeconomics Society (Box 8)
  - Bishops (Box 8)
  - Pastoral Letter on Catholic Social Teaching (Box 8)
  - Bundeskanzler Fellowship (Box 8)
  - Canadian Institute for Advanced Research (Box 8)
  - Economic Growth and Policy (Box 8)
  - Center for European Studies, 1990-91 (Box 40)
  - Center for Foundational Studies (Box 9)
  - Center for National Policy, 1981-1987 (Box 40)
  - Center for Operations Research and Econometrics (CORE) (Box 9)
  - Center for Risk Analysis (Box 9)
  - Center for Study in Israel (Box 9)
  - Centre d'Etudes Prospectives d'Economie Mathématique Appliquées a la Planification (CEPREMAP) (Box 9)
  - CEPR Search, 1989 (Box 40)
  - City College of New York (Box 9)
  - City College-Minorities Center (Box 9)
  - City College Reunion, 1990 (Box 40)
  - City College-Scholarship endowment (Box 9)
  - Charles River Associates (Box 9)
  - Committee for Economic Recovery (Box 9)
  - Delhi School of Economics (Box 9)
  - East-West Center (Box 9)
  - Econometrics Society (Box 9)
  - Econometrics Society-continued (Box 9)